Guide to the World Student Christian Federation Europe Region Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
World Student Christian Federation Europe Region records
1953-2013
RG 46E
Yale University Divinity School Library
36
(87 boxes)
The archives of the World Student Christian Federation Europe Region include administrative records, minutes, financial records, and documentation of conferences, workshops, and projects such as the Theological Project, Women's Project, Refugee Project, and East European Language and Leadership Training Project (Lingua Franca).
World Student Christian Federation. Europe Office
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the WSCF Europe Region, 2012, 2017
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
The World Student Christian Federation (WSCF) was founded in 1895 with the aim of uniting movements or associations of Christian students throughout the world. Since 1968 the WSCF has been decentralized into regions. There are currently six regions, each with its own regional office: Africa, Asia Pacific, Europe, Latin America and the Caribbean, Middle East, North America and Canada.
WSCF Europe is part of a global federation of grassroot Student Christian Movements (SCMs). These local organizations work on campuses and nationally to bring Christian students from all denominations together to work on issues of social justice. As a global organization the World Student Christian Federation connects SCMs through events, networks and solidarity/advocacy work. The WSCF Europe Region brings together students from 21 Student Christian Movements across Europe through international conferences, campaigns, and publications.
Scope and Contents
These are the official archives of the World Student Christian Federation Europe Regional Office. The records have been organized as received, primarily according to a classification system provided by the WSCF Europe Region Office. They include administrative records, minutes, financial records, and documentation of conferences, workshops, and projects such as the Theological Project, Women's Project, Refugee Project, and East European Language and Leadership Training Project (Lingua Franca). An addendum to the collection integrated in 2017 contains similar documentation and has been retained primarily in the order in which it was received. There is considerable overlap between the various sub-series of the addendum.
Arrangement
I. Conferences and Events
II. Committee Records / Reports
III. Publications
IV. Correspondence with SCMs
V. WSCF Interregional Records
VI. Projects / Working Groups
VII. Correspondence with Other Organizations
VIII. Administrative and Fundraising Records
IX. Related Organizations
X. Addendum 2017
Youth in the ecumenical movement -- Europe; World Student Christian Federation. Europe Office
- Conferences and Events, Series I
  - European Students Conference, Series I
    - 1.1 Lillehammer: "The Witness of the Gospel in the Class Struggle", 1975
      - 1.1.1 Lectures, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1.1.2 Reports, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1.1.3 Resolutions, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1.1.4 Program, papers, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1.1.5 Papers, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1.2 Cardiff: "Facing the Future: Rethinking Christian Spirituality in Political Involvement", 1979
      - 1.2.1 Reports and letters, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1.2.2 Preparations, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 1.2.3 Program, papers, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1.2 Athens: "Ten Years After: Higher Education and Student Work in 1978"
      - 1.2.4 Program, papers, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 1.2.5 Preparatory materials, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1.2.6 Letters, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1.2 Linho, Portugal: "The Beginning of the Doing", 1976
      - 1.2.7 Reports, 1976, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1.3 El Escorial, Madrid: "Salt of the Earth?", 1981
      - 1.3.1 Reports, press, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 1.3.2 Speeches, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - 1.3.3 Workshops and groups (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - 1.3.4 Preparatory papers (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - 1.3.5 Moon theatrical performance (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - 1.3.5 Preparatory meeting (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - 1.4.5 (should be 1.3.5) Finances (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - 1.4.6 (should be 1.3.6) Invitations (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1.4 Rome: "Racism in Europe", 1983
      - 1.4.1 Reports (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - 1.4.2 Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - 1.4.3 Preparatory documents / interpreters (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - 1.4.4 Finances (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 1.5 Valamo: "'Coming up for Air': Our self-understanding as a Student Christian Movement", 1985
      - 1.5.1 Reports, minutes (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 1.5.2 Preparatory papers, letters (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - 1.5.3 Speeches and workshops (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - 1.5.4 Participants, speakers, invitations (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - 1.5.5 Committee Valamo, correspondence (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - 1.5.6 Finances, interpreters (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - 1.5.7 Evaluations (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - 1.5.8 Photographs (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 1.6 Boldern: "Europe: Unfinished Business", 1987
      - 1.6.1 Reports (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - 1.6.2 Preparatory materials (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - 1.6.3 Finances (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - 1.6.4 Registration / invitations (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - 1.6.5 Letters (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - WSCF Europe Conference
    - Leadership Training Conference - Racism in the International Context - Strasbourg, France, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Leadership, Authoritarianism and Neo-Facism - Strasbourg, France, 1984 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - 1.7.1 International Summer School on African History and Solidarity Work - Haughton, Norway, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 1.7.2 Education - For What? - Strasbourg, France, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 1.7.3 Living with Technology - Milan, Italy, 1985 Oct (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 1.7.4 Everything is Possible: Genetic Engineering from a Politial and Theological Perspective - Strasbourg, France, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 1.7.5 Human Rights and Participation in Society - Berlin, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 1.7.6 European Ecumenical Assembly - Basel, Switzerland, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 1.7.7 SYNDESMOS-WSCF Consultation: Christian Witness of Youth in Pluralistic Society: Orthodox and Protestant Youth Encounter - Yugoslavia, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 1.8.1 Conference on Nationalism - Austria, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 1.8.2 Consultation on Resources and Finances - Woudschoten, Netherlands, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 1.8.3 Beyond the Boundaries: The Economic and Social Consequences of the Single European Act - Strasbourg, France, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 1.8.4 Refugees in Europe: The impplications of the Single European Act - Lisbon, Portugal, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 1.9.1 Europe / Latin America Consultation - Quito, Ecuador, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 1.9.2 Communications Consultation - Bievres, France, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 1.9.3 Spirituality - Courage and Challenge: Women's Seminar WSCF- Europe / EYCE - Luhanka, Finland, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 1.9.4 Higher Education in Europe - Strasbourg, France, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 1.9.5 Ethnic Minorities - Budapest, Hungary, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 1.9.6 Let Us Survive: Ecological Consequences of the Single European Act - Strasbourg, France, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - "Big E" (The Big Event)
    - 1.10 /1.13 Seeds of Hope - European Student Festival - finances - Birmingham, UK, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - UK - evaluations, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - UK - program, addresses, worship, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - UK - preparatory committee, correspondence, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - UK - applications, program, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - UK - applications, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - UK - evaluations, reports, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - UK - program, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - UK - evaluation, preparations, resources, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - UK - interpreters, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1.11 / 1.12 Many Gifts, One Spirit. Spirituality and Rationalism: Searching for a Balance - Woudschoten, Netherlands -fundraising correspondence, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Netherlands - reports, publications, preparations, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Netherlands - reports, publications, preparations, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Netherlands - address lists, donors, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Netherlands - finances, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - WSCF Europe Conference
    - 1.14.1 Europe/Latin America Consultation - Looking 500 Years Ahead - Loures, Portugal, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 1.14.2 Bible and Theology in the Federation - Bossey, Switzerland, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 1.14.3 Women and Finances - Hungary, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 1.14.4 Facing New Poverty in Europe: Christian Realities and Economic Values - Storkow, Germany, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 1.14.5 Berlin conference, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 1.14.6 Conference on Xenophobia, Nationalism and Racism - Vienna, Austria Peripheries in Europe - Strasbourg, France, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 1.14.7 Europe-Africa Forum: Higher Education - Commodity or Community - Germany, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 1.14.7 Various conferences, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 1.15.1 WSCF Berlin conference, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 1.15.2 WSCF Conference on Ecumenism - Crete, Greece, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - 1.15.3 Gender Conference - Strasbourg, France, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - 1.15.4 WSCF Consultation on Education and Contemporary Social Issues; International Youth Consultation on Social Development - Copenhagen, Denmark, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - 1.15.5 On the Edge of Life - Strasbourg, France, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - 1.15.6 North-Western Leadership Training Programme - Amsterdam, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 1.15.7 Between Heaven and Earth: God, Ethics, and Sexuality - Wiston Lodge, Scotland, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 1.15.8 Living with a Fact: An Introduction to Conflict and Conflict Resolution - Prali, Italy, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 1.15.9 Living Together, Different Histories - Santa Severa (Rome), Italy, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 1.15.10 Do You Know What You are Reading? Understanding the Bible in the 1990s - Espoo, Finland, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 1.15.11 Consultation on the Participation of Orthodox Movements in WSCF Europe - Athens, Greece, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 1.15.12 WSCF, EYCE, CEC Joint Study Session: 2nd Consultation - Reconciliation: The Christian Vision for a New Living Together in Europe - Strasbourg, France, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 1.15.13 Women and Spirituality - Evro Youth Centre, ca. 1997 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 1.16.1 Freedom and Authority - Minsk, Belarus, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 1.16.2 East and West, North and South - Gender Conference - Romania, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 1.16.3 Borderlines: In Search of an Ecumenical Vision for Europe - Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - 1.16.4 Encounters: Central and Eastern European Conference - Piliscsaba, Hungary, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 1.16.5 ValuesQ Loss or Change? - Budapest, Hungary, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 1.16.7 European Issues - What Kind of Europe Do We Want? - Strasbourg, France, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - WSCF Europe Events
    - 1.17.1 Staff and officers meeting - Budapest, Hungary, 2002, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - 1.17.2 Staff and officers meetings, 1996-1999 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - 1.17.3 Staff and Board meetings, 1993, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - 1.17.4 Staff and Board members Consultation on Ecumenism - Birmingham-Wales, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - 1.17.5 Consultation for staff and Board members on Leadership Training - Czech Republic, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 1.17.6 meeting of staff working group for the Global Ecumenical Youth Gathering, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 1.17.7 European Inter-Secretariat meetings, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - 1.17.8 Ecumenical Youth Consultation - Bossey, Switzerland, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - 1.17.9 Women's Camp Agape, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - 1.17.10 European University Chaplains Conference meetings, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Committee Records / Reports, Series II
  - 2.1.1 European Regional Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 2.1.2 European Regional Committee, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 2.1.3 European Regional Committee, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 2.1.4 European Regional Committee, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 2.1.5 European Regional Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 2.1.6 European Regional Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 2.1.7 European Regional Committee, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 2.2.1 European Standing Committee correspondence: Committee circulars, 1978-1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 2.2.2 European Standing Committee correspondence: Treasurer, 1978-1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 2.2.3 European Standing Committee correspondence: Chairperson, 1978-1983 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 2.2.4 European Standing Committee Correspondence: Milan Opocensky, 1978-1983 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 2.2.5 European Standing Committee correspondence: Re. General Assembly, 1981, 1978-1983 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 2.2.6 European Standing Committee correspondence: various, 1978-1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 2.3.1 Europe Committee and Standing Committee preparations, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 2.3.2 Europe Committee and Standing Committee preparations, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 2.3.3 European Standing Committee and Regional Committee - Geneva, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 2.3.4 European Standing Committee and Regional Committee, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 2.3.5 European Standing Committee and Regional Committee - Woudschoten, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 2.4.1 European Regional Committee preparations, correspondence, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 2.4.2 European Regional Committee preparations, correspondence, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 2.4.3 European Regional Committee preparations, correspondence, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 2.5.1 European Regional Committee preparations, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 2.5.2 European Regional Committee letters, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 2.5.3 European Regional Committee reports, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 2.6.1 Records of meetings: European Student Chaplains Conferences, European Students' Conference, 1953-1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 2.6.2 Records of meetings: European Regional Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 2.6.3 Records of meetings: European Regional Assembly, European Regional Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 2.6.4 Records of meetings: European Regional Assembly, 1983, 1985
  - 2.7.1 European Regional Committee preparations, correspondence, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 2.7.2 European Regional Committee events, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 2.7.3 European Regional Committee correspondence, minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 2.7.4 European Regional Committee correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 2.7.5 WSCF Europe Region Constitution; European Regional Committee events, 1983-1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 2.8.1 WSCF European Committee minutes, 1969-1973 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 2.8.2 WSCF European Committee, European Standing Committee minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 14A, Folder 1)
  - 2.8.3 European Standing Committee minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 14A, Folder 2)
  - 2.9.1 European Regional Committee and European Standing Committee minutes, 1980-1984 (Box 14A, Folder 3)
  - 2.9.2 European Regional Committee and European Standing Committee minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 14A, Folder 4)
  - 2.9.3 European Regional Committee and European Standing Committee minutes, 1987-1989 (Box 14A, Folder 5)
  - 2.10.1 Movement visitation: staff reports, 1981-1983 (Box 14A, Folder 6)
  - 2.10.2 Miscellaneous reports, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 2.10.3 Miscellaneous reports, 1977-1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 2.11.1 Self-understanding of WSCF Europe Region - memos, reports, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 2.11.2 Self-understanding of WSCF Europe Region - memos, reports, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 2.12.1 Miscellaneous historical documents, 1960s-1970s (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 2.12.2 Miscellaneous historical documents, 1970s (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 2.12.3 Miscellaneous historical documents, 1980s (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - History of the Hungarian Student Christian Movement 1907-1920, by Draskoczy Istvan (in Hungarian), 1977 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - 2.13.1 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1979-1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 2.13.2 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 2.13.3 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 2.13.4 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 2.14.1 European Regional Assembly - Hirschluch, Germany, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 2.14.1 European Regional Assembly - Hirschluch, Germany, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 2.14.2 European Regional Assembly - Florence, Italy, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 2.14.2 European Regional Assembly - Florence, Italy, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 2.15.1 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 2.15.2 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 2.15.3 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - 2.15.4 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 2.15.5 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 2.16.1 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 2.16.2 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 2.16.2 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 2.16.2 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 2.16.3 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 2.16.4 European Regional Committee documents, correspondence, minutes, 1998-2001 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - 2.17.1 European Regional Assembly - Sweden, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - 2.17.2 European Regional Assembly - Romania, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 2.17.3 European Regional Assembly - Norway, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Publications, Series III
  - 3.3.1 "Before the Cock Crows: Biblical and Theological Reflection in the Student Christian Movements in Europe Today", 1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 3.3.2 Correspondence related to "Before the Cock Crows", 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 3.3.3 Booklets and reports, including "Gladly We Rebel", "Women Doing Theology", "Students and the Life and Mission of the Church", Study documents, 1964-1991 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 3.3.4 Booklets and reports, including "Addis-Abeba to Colombo WSCF-Europe (1972-1976)", "Towards a Women's History in the World Student Christian Federation", 1977-1995 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 3.4.1 WSCF Journal "Europhoria": correspondence, articles, graphics, etc., 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - 3.4.1 WSCF Journal "Europhoria": correspondence, articles, graphics, etc., 1990 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Correspondence with SCMs, Series IV
  - 4.7.1 Miscellaneous, 1980-1998 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 4.7.2 Great Britain SCM, 1986-1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 4.7.3 Belarus, Greece, Ireland, Austria, Germany, Czech Republic, Netherlands; questionnaires to national movements, 1988-1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - 4.8.1 Circular letters to national movements, 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - 4.8.2 Circular letters to national movements, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 4.9.1 Circular letters to national movements, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 4.9.2 Circular letters to national movements, 1984-1988 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 4.9.3 Circular letters to national movements, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- WSCF Interregional Records, Series V
  - 5.1.1 WSCF Executive Committee minutes, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 5.1.2 WSCF Executive Committee minutes, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 5.1.3 WSCF Executive Committee minutes, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 5.2.1 WSCF Executive Committee minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 5.2.2 WSCF Executive Committee minutes, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 5.3.1 WSCF Executive Committee minutes, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 5.3.2 WSCF Executive Committee minutes, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 5.3.3 WSCF Executive Committee minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - 5.4.1 WSCF Executive Committee minutes, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - 5.4.2 WSCF Executive Committee minutes, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 5.4.3 WSCF Executive Committee minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 5.5.1 WSCF General Assembly - Mexico, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - 5.5.2 WSCF General Assembly - Mexico, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - 5.5.3 WSCF General Assembly - Mexico, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 5.6.1 Interregional correspondence with IRO (WSCF central office), 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 5.6.2 Interregional correspondence with IRO, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 5.7.1 Interregional correspondence with IRO, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 5.7.2 Interregional correspondence with IRO, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 5.7.3 Interregional correspondence with IRO, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 5.8.1 Interregional correspondence with IRO, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 5.8.2 Interregional correspondence with IRO, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 5.8.3 Interregional correspondence with IRO, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 5.9.1 Interregional correspondence with other regions: Africa, Asia, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - 5.9.2 Interregional correspondence with other regions: Latin America, Middle East, North America, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 5.10.1 Interregional correspondence with other regions: Africa, Asia, 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 5.10.2 Interregional correspondence with other regions: Latin America, 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 5.10.3 Interregional correspondence with other regions: Middle East, North America, 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 5.11.1 Interregional correspondence with other regions: Africa, 1986-1989 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 5.11.2 Interregional correspondence with other regions: Asia-Pacific, Latin America, Middle East, 1986-1989 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 5.11.3 Interregional correspondence with other regions: North America, 1986-1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 5.12.1 IRO Executive Committee correspondence with WSCF Europe, 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - 5.12.2 IRO Executive Committee correspondence with WSCF Europe, 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 5.12.3 IRO Executive Committee correspondence with WSCF Europe, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 5.12.4 IRO Executive Committee correspondence with WSCF Europe, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - 5.12.5 IRO Executive Committee correspondence with WSCF Europe, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - 5.13.1 Post General Assembly visits, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - 5.13.2 Post General Assembly visits, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 5.14.1 WSCF Global Executive Committee meeting (with Senior Friends)- Geneva, Switzerland, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 5.14.2 WSCF Global Executive Committee meeting - St. Louis, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - 5.14.2 WSCF Global Executive Committee meeting - St. Louis, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 5.15.1 WSCF Global Executive Committee meeting - Harare, Zimbabwe; IRO correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - 5.15.2 WSCF Global Executive Committee meeting - Cairo, Egypt, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - 5.15.3 Interregional correspondence/reports: Africa, Latin America, Middle East, 1994-1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)